Doing that domino effect is the
potential for the $1.2 trillion
of student loans to impact the
mortgage market small business
formation future retirement
security and much more
when people's income is being
soaked up by their student debt
payments that means
less money they can
and save for retirement
for a down payment
and it may mean that they're
less willing to take a risk
to start a small business
or to try something new
the top piece the advice I can
give to streamline borrowers
is if you're in
trouble do not lead
the telephone calls or the way.
Let's take action.
You go to consumer finance
staff at the end user are paying
for college platform, which
with a few clicks of the button
to help you navigate
different repayment options
and I'll probably default.
A lot of people are eligible
for income base repayment
and may not even you
can go to student loans
these dots and estimate
how much your payment might
be under this program and you
can even electronically five
you can also call your
student loan servicer
and ask them for more
information about it.