If you make a deal
with the devil
on releasing those
five tell them
I think this was a
very hard choice, which
is why I think my
book is so aptly named
if you look at what the factors.
We're going into the
decision of course,
there are competing
interests and values.
One of our values is
we bring everybody home
off the battlefield.
The best we can
it doesn't matter
how they ended up in a
prisoner of war situation
it doesn't matter
does not matter.
We bring our people home
how was your health.
It's very good.
Thank you how
serious it was really
wasn't that I think
a serious concussion.
I ran into congressman Paul Ryan
at the inauguration last year.
And I had ready was
this great athlete
and I said they did you have
a concussion goes oh yes he
said I had several I think
three in the last one mysterious
but my mother was smart enough
to make me stay in it what
happens to athletes soldiers
young people in car accidents
all the reasons why people
get concussions if they come
to shake it off and I felt like
you get back UPI can go to work
and the doctor said, no,
you're going to stay and rest
because then you will have a
complete recovery because you'd
have a club and you're right.
I can't retract my related yes
so blood thinners but senators
for life probably but I don't
mind, because I don't ever
want to have to go
through that again.
So no lingering effect
no lingering effect
of it what would you like to say
to Carl wrote about your brain
that I know he was
called Bush's brain
in one of the books
written about him.
And I wish him well
change is great to be
our age Mitch McConnell
said at one point,
the 2016 will be the
return Golden Girls
that was a very popular
long running TV series.